<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mystica on Home</title>
    <link>http://mysticazhang.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mystica on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 23:25:05 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://mysticazhang.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>实习作品合辑</title>
      <link>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20180422/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 23:25:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20180422/</guid>
      <description>It took me a long time to learn where he came from. The little prince, who asked me so many questions, never seemed to hear the ones I asked him. It was from words dropped by chance that, little by little, everything was revealed to me. The first time he saw my airplane, for instance (I shall not draw my airplane; that would be much too complicated for me), he asked me:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>对于找工作、暑期实习的些许观点</title>
      <link>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20180412/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 23:27:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20180412/</guid>
      <description>We are introduced to the narrator, a pilot, and his ideas about grown-ups
Once when I was six years old I saw a magnificent picture in a book, called True Stories from Nature, about the primeval forest. It was a picture of a boa constrictor in the act of swallowing an animal. Here is a copy of the drawing.
In the book it said: &amp;ldquo;Boa constrictors swallow their prey whole, without chewing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git更新个人主页内容</title>
      <link>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20180411/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 23:25:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20180411/</guid>
      <description>I showed my masterpiece to the grown-ups, and asked them whether the drawing frightened them.
But they answered: &amp;ldquo;Frighten? Why should any one be frightened by a hat?&amp;rdquo;
My drawing was not a picture of a hat. It was a picture of a boa constrictor digesting an elephant. But since the grown-ups were not able to understand it, I made another drawing: I drew the inside of the boa constrictor, so that the grown-ups could see it clearly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netease Game Telephone Interview</title>
      <link>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20180410/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 15:25:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20180410/</guid>
      <description>April 4th, the hr from Netease Game called me for appointing an interview date, and today a young lady called me at 15:00.
This is my interview experience, just for reference only!
 A brief Self-introduction first;
 Talk me about a case in Netease Reader you have joined;
 3 words to describe yourself, and why? (well-knit; innovation; careful )
 Give me an example for your innovation;
 Do you play any games?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>一座小镇</title>
      <link>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20171204/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 23:58:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20171204/</guid>
      <description>I ask the indulgence of the children who may read this book for dedicating it to a grown-up. I have a serious reason: he is the best friend I have in the world. I have another reason: this grown-up understands everything, even books about children. I have a third reason: he lives in France where he is hungry and cold. He needs cheering up. If all these reasons are not enough, I will dedicate the book to the child from whom this grown-up grew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://mysticazhang.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mysticazhang.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Tel: +86 17621618096
Email: mystica0809@foxmail.com
You can leave your messages, I will contact quickly!
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>在新一线城市做短租房东</title>
      <link>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20160303%E6%96%B0%E4%B8%80%E7%BA%BF/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mysticazhang.github.io/post/20160303%E6%96%B0%E4%B8%80%E7%BA%BF/</guid>
      <description>It took me a long time to learn where he came from. The little prince, who asked me so many questions, never seemed to hear the ones I asked him. It was from words dropped by chance that, little by little, everything was revealed to me. The first time he saw my airplane, for instance (I shall not draw my airplane; that would be much too complicated for me), he asked me:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>